Good Morning
Good morning
Today's
Release Event in Musashi Murayama
It will be held at AEON MALL Musashi Murayama
I thought it was a great angle.
It's too weird angle.
It's...
Ah, Wakaemi.
Good morning.
We're all sitting around the table today.
There was a terrible silence.
My lips were all pouting, but I didn't go first.
You've all memorized the song.
But you know what?
I haven't even explained the chorus yet.
I think they're just enjoying watching the music video.
Today is the first performance of "I WANNA" in front of the audience.
In front of the audience.
I thought I'd give a lecture on singing together in front of the audience.
So we're having a meeting right now.
Let's have a scene from the meeting.
Let's have the red fruit sing.
Red berries
Red berries from red berries.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
All right, let's finish it.
And fake fake fake fake.
That's a lot of fakes.
Zella zella hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
Can't beat that sparkle.
Follow me. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Can you do it?
You want to try one?
Okay?
Yeah.
We'll do it. How about a battle next time?
What a day off today, brother.
It's true, the theme changes every time.
Oh, man...
It's on youtube.
It's on youtube. We're going to make it our own today.
And since it's our first performance today, we're going to do it ourselves.
I want to see me. I'm getting used to that part, but I wanted to be conscious of it.
I want to see me for the first time.
We've already done some filming.
As for the excitement, we made a lot of eye contact.
I think it's going to be fun.
It's been a while since I've performed on stage, so I might tend to be a bit relaxed.
I'll make sure to make the right decisions, and make sure I'm on top of it.
Go, go, go, go!
I'm going to use an Aladdin airplane in this event video.
Old Dress Finbar
Nurburng in Horizon
Hello everyone! This is Gaz Gaz!
Thank you!
We are having a showdown for the king of Dotch in the song "Dotch" from Accelerate.
We are having a project called "Which one is the king of Dotch?
Which one has the funniest MC?
Each MC will be the MC for a release event to be held in Japan.
We're going to split up the MCs for our nationwide release events and let everyone who comes to the event decide which one is the funniest!
Please listen carefully to the MC's as they will be split up.
We will be doing it again today.
Let's go to the performance now!
Please listen to it!
Amami Anchal
Appy needed
Thanos
Now then, let's hear the Italic
Let's start!
What I did on my recent vacation
Well, let's just do a simple "pom-pom" this time
OK, OK, OK
Let's do it like a rhythm game
Okay.
Jang-jang, jang-jang, jang-jang, jang-jang...
OK, let's do it.
Let's do it, everyone.
That's right.
Let's do it!
Amusement park and illumination!
Sleeping!
Naptime walk!
School!
What did you do on your day off?
Tell me about your day off.
What do you mean?
Did you really go to school on your day off?
I didn't go.
What?
We were talking about the weekdays.
Let's do it again.
Revenge.
One more time, from Yokachan.
Amusement park and illumination!
Sleeping!
Naptime walk!
You were sleeping!
That's it!
Thank you!
Well, let's get to it, shall we?
Let's hear it!
Dodge!
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la.
What's a lie, what's the truth
One more subject
Imosho fiction to create
You want one, too, don't you?
I love you, Raomi
La la la la, front and back
If you show me everything, I'll show you more
Lala la la la, front and back
Show me everything.
You know what this show is called? Hey, guys.
You know what it is?
No?
I mean, what did you do on your day off?
Okay, then.
From Claire.
I, uh...
I went to visit my parents' dog and cat.
I took the day off.
And since it was a school vacation.
I thought this would be a good time to go.
I went home.
I had given them a story, didn't I?
You were so cute!
I posted it on my Instagram too.
I also went to see the illumination with my friends.
As for me...
I spent my last day off doing maintenance work.
I'm not messing around with my aesthetics.
I'm not messing with it.
I'm not messing with anything.
That's not the kind of maintenance I'm talking about.
It's more like going to the sun.
I go to the beach about once a week.
Oh, really?
Yeah, I get my ecology done.
I don't...
I went shopping with my family.
I ate a lot of barbecued meat.
And Gobi?
I got a new accessory.
Oh, no, I made a mistake.
Spontaneous.
I'm spontaneous.
Did you guys have a good time?
Thank you very much.
Please vote for me.
The youngest, please.
I'll perform there.
No, no, no.
Let me perform with you.
I'll do it with you.
Yes, so...
Chie was the youngest
Thank you very much
So, let's see
Which one of you was funnier just now?
We are waiting for your vote on the X side.
And we are also looking for talk topics from everyone
I hope you will send me many of them!
Yes, this will be the last song!
But...
What a surprise!
It will be performed here for the first time!
For the first time!
Have you seen the music video?
I'm glad you guys saw it.
I'm so glad!
Please watch it!
If you haven't seen it yet, I hope you'll watch it a lot!
Let's end on a high note!
Please listen to it!
I wanna sing it
Thank you very much for coming today.
Thank you very much.
See you again!
That's all for now.
Thank you very much.
See you again.
We're done with the revue. We're going to the benefit now.
This is Bobo, the blonde. She's cute.
There's a bit of a face deviation.
You know, I'm sure all the Us fans had the same reaction.
We all had the same reaction.
Wait a minute.
That's amazing!
Taiwan's declaration.
Today... today... when she introduced the song...
Misaki was doing this
But maybe she's alone.
Yeah, she kind of left right away.
Did you make a mistake?
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll say it alone.
Oh, that's good.
Dad used to drink 2 liters of water.
1.5.
I recommend 1.5, everyone!
Why?
2 liters isn't much.
It's too much!
Two liters is a lot!
Two liters?
If I take it off, my stomach will be full.
It's a little too much.
One and a half is just right.
I see.
This way, sir.
Please drink it.
Here you go.
Hey.
What is this guy doing?
It was fun.
It's been a while since I've seen you.
It's true.
It's been about a week.
Yes, sir.
Please tell me what you thought.
We were having our usual MC competition.
But then I decided to put my knees on the stage.
I was going to sit on my knees on the stage.
It's a story about a day off.
So...
I said, "Let's sit on the stage.
She praised me.
I'm glad.
It was a fresh and fun event!
Who had a good time today?
Yay!
Thank you